<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<update version="0.0.1">
			<file name="items.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/aobeirne20/aurora-homebrew/main/user-augur/gifts-of-origination/items.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>
	<element name="Chronomancer's Pearls" type="Magic Item" source="Gifts of Origination" id="ID_AUGR_GORG_MAGIC_ITEM_CHRONOMANCERS_PEARLS">
		<description>
			<p>Suspended chronomatic energy, captured in pearl-like spheres that offer glimpses of histories past and still to be.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong><em>Temporal Retreat.</em></strong> Each pearl can be crushed once, as a bonus action, to instantly jump the local area (1000 ft. sphere) back 5 minutes in time. This undoes all damage, conditions, and death, and resets all interactions. It removes any items gained, and restores any items lost. </p>
			<p>The gift itself is comprised of three pearls, which are consumed after use. The recreation of the previous moment is to be done as accurately as can be remembered, with the DM having final judgment.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="category">Wondrous Items</set>
			<set name="cost" currency="gp">0</set>
			<set name="weight" lb="0">0 lb.</set>
			<set name="type">Wondrous Item</set>
			<set name="rarity">Origination Gift</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Xyston of Annihilation" type="Magic Item" source="Gifts of Origination" id="ID_AUGR_GORG_MAGIC_ITEM_XYSTON_OF_ANNIHILATION">
		<description>
			<p>A long, lightweight spear-like weapon made of a material unknown to this plane. Resonates with the latent energies trapped inside.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong><em>Entity Annihilation.</em></strong> As an action, the xyston can be pointed at a target. By unleashing the contained energy, the first being in the path of the weapon is totally annihilated by the beam, eradicating it and any items or gear it was using. This damage is unmitigatable and will never fails to kill the target. In the process, the energy released also results in the destruction of the xyston.</p>

		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="category">Wondrous Items</set>
			<set name="cost" currency="gp">0</set>
			<set name="weight" lb="3">3 lb.</set>
			<set name="type">Wondrous Item</set>
			<set name="rarity">Origination Gift</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
</elements>

Gifts given:
Roll randomly at beginning of the game
1-3 Players: 1 Gift
4+ Players: 2 Gifts

Other gifts:
Tesseract of Translocation (movement power)
Mind Spike (temporary perfect mind control)
Mirror (become visible entity for ~10 minutes)
Experimental Titanium Formula no.4 (invincibility)
Puzzle box (solve puzzle, recieved answer to any question)


